Please explain a little to my wife.  She fights with her mother a
little more.  What has
happened?
From whose mother?
From my mother.
battle.
Why do you fight?
Guruji is lying.
[coughing]
[laughter] When he
talks a little loudly,
Mom gets a little upset.
How do you speak mother-in-law?
No.
Guruji, did you not bring water?
Where is the salt kept?  Mother-in-law [laughs]
speaks like that.   There are
no.
How do you talk to your mother-in-law? Not by shouting, not in a
high voice, think carefully, speak in such a way that it
calms down the mind and others, you become
calm, well
if we can make someone happy by speaking then
tell me is there any expense, that is
why speak in such a way, speak in a nice way that
everyone likes it,
well
tomorrow you will also become a mother-in-law, you will also get a daughter-in-law, what you say
is right [laughs] if
he speaks to you in a high voice,
you will only feel bad.
That's why the mother-in-law also wants some happiness from her daughter-in-law.
Okay,
give some happiness to your mother-in-law.  Now
what happiness will you give by shouting?
[laughs]
Maiya, say it lovingly, Maa ji, Maa
ji.  Isn't it?  On one hand you call me mother.
You say she is my mother.
What has happened?  What am I hearing?
So you shout on the other side.  [laughs]
Relationships have become a formality these days.
Good.   The one whom
we call mother, treat her like a mother.
Once we call someone sister, we will
maintain a sisterly relationship with her throughout our life.
Or is it just that I said it was a joke?
No [laughs]
No jokes in relationships.  Relationship means
relationship.  It is a fact.
My son drinks a lot of alcohol.  The daughter-in-law
is also sitting here.  Very upset.
What has happened?  [laughter] What am
I hearing?   Get me to
talk.  What is your name?
Discretion.
Vivek, you are the Vivek.  So you drink alcohol every day
?
Or
what do you earn?  How much do you earn?   I
earn ₹600.
Good!
₹600
Yes.
What do you do with ₹600 a day?   I
sell liquor.
Hey! God.  [laughter] Do
you sell liquor?  The only good work is to sell.
So you must be telling the customers after drinking it.  Look,
I drank it and gave it to you.
[laughs]
So before giving it to the customers, they would open the lid and
drink it and then give it to them.  Isn't it?
Mixing water
[laughs]
So you also sell liquor mixed with water?
Yes sir.
Just think, water is not mixed in milk.  It is
also mixed in liquor.  [laughter]
So, how does the water get locked in the bottle
?   He
takes his goods in open form, not in bottles.
Open
well.
So you sell Paa?
Yes, Tra.
So why do you drink?  After drinking he has some
strength to speak.  [music]
What?
Hey, I don't drink alcohol but still I talk all day long.   If a
customer shouts, he has to speak.
So you see, customers are talking to us every day, they
talk all day long.  We do
n't drink.
Come on mother, I swear.
Now this liquor seller should also stop working.
Do something else.  You can earn Rs 600 anywhere.   It
is a fact.  [laughter] That's what I'll have to do.
Tell me whether drinking alcohol is right or wrong.
This is wrong.   It
is wrong.
What's wrong with alcohol?  Tell.
What's wrong with alcohol?  The brain does not work.   Does
n't work.  So why do you drink when you know
?  [laughter]
That hand shakes for this.
Hey! God.   Does your
hand tremble?
Yes.   Then if I
drink it I will start mumbling.
So your hands don't tremble after drinking?   Will
not tremble.
[laughter]
So this is a medicine for shaking hands?   Do you make your
wife drink alcohol too?
What has happened?  What am I hearing?
No.
And does dad drink alcohol?   No. No.   If you were
teaching Bhagavad Gita
then why did you become bad brother [laughs]
father reads Bhagavad Gita,
everything became good because of the lockdown,
now leave this liquor shop, leave your job, do some
other
work, earn Rs. 000 per month, that means Rs. 000 per day,
what is the problem
or
but now I swear to my mother that you will not drink alcohol,
all those who drink alcohol have been ruined,
well I have taught them, they are
troubled, if someone's life would improve by drinking alcohol
then all those who drink alcohol would be on the right
path.   A
good
drinker doesn't work.  He remains poor.   Does
not give time to family.  Children become orphans.
Oh my God [laughs] I ca
n't read or write.  Come son, life is
given by God.  The body is precious.  One day the body does
not exist.
Or the
person dies.  [music]
What?   One
should move ahead by doing good work.
What will you get by drinking alcohol?
[laughter]
Your body was so good before.  Now look, it has
dried completely.   I made a
big mistake, sir.
So is alcohol bothering you or not?
So no more drinking.  If you want, you can give up alcohol.
Well,
and when you quit, the society will learn from you
that look, Vivek ji has quit drinking, so
why can't we?  You will become an inspiration for the society.
[laughter]
I wanted to ask, you have a lot of women who are
crazy about you.  What has happened?
Because you are so beautiful and powerful.
What am I hearing?   Have
you ever had a crush on someone?
[laughs] Have
you ever had a crush on anyone?
What is a crush?   Has
anyone made you crazy?
I am crazy about you and God.  He is crazy about God.
No, there are women who are crazy about you.
[laughter]
The gopis came.  Hey, all of them are our mothers and sisters.   No
one is crazy.
Hey, did you never come?  [laughter]
Maiya, I am asking, have you come to Vrindavan?   No no, I had come to
visit.   So
what are you seeing?  The opposite
[laughs]
came to my mind that if this happens to you sometimes, then
you are also a human being, right?   Do you
understand?   Do you
understand?
Yes, they are humans.
Yes.  So we have married every human being to someone or the other.
You are our
wife.
So is she your wife?  [laughter]
Lives with his wife.  Why don't you
know?
No, I didn't know.
Hey Ram Ram Ram.  [laughter]
So is our wife.  Lives with his wife.  There are
children too.  Give what God has given you.
Well, God gave it.  [laughter]
Why?  Whose gift are you?
No, we are not given by God.  I am a gift from my father and
mother.  [laughter]
So your father went into your mother's womb to
make you.
No.  [Laughter]
Yes, it
is actually a scientific process.  There is a
scientific process in it.
Yes, there is a scientific process by which the
sperm goes in.
Meaning the scientist went into your mother's womb.
[laughter]
No, the scientists didn't go.  Dad's
sperm was gone.
Yes.  [laughter]
So how did they become water?  Which eye
became what it was?  How were the eyes formed?   He must have been the one who
made it.
That is the third power.
Who is he?  They say that there is God
but other Muslims now say that there is Khuda,
different people say different things.
Muslims believe in God, we believe in God, so there is only
one God, it
means you do not believe in God,
CM is trapped,
I believe in Him, but there is a third power that I believe in this only, so it
means who was the one who created you in your mother's womb
?
I believe that when my parents met,
I was born, this is
true.
Who did the further processing?
Hey, what do you want to say?  The further
process gets created automatically in the stomach.
Well, it happens on its own.
How will it happen automatically?  Tell me, can your
clothes be made without being made?
No.
Well, can your mobile be made without making it?
No.  Your glasses can be made without being made.
All these things make a man.
When cloth cannot be made without making it.  If a mobile phone
cannot be made then how would you have been made without it
?  Just think about this.
[laughter] There's
someone who made you too.
His name is God.  You said a very good thing.   Do
n't you believe in God?   I
agree.
Come on mother's [laughs]
so you third power which is the contribution of the parents in the mother's womb is so much
that
only the parents' company happened through them.  After that, who is the creator of the creation that took place
from the drop of water
?  I just want to tell you this.   That's
right [laughs].  Who is it?  That's what you
said, God is there.   Did
you understand now?
Yes sir.   I didn't know it
before.
According to you, I am made by God.
And according to me,
now it seems that it must have been made by God himself.
Then science failed here.
[laughter]
Maharaj Ji, I get very angry.
What has happened?
So what do you do?  In anger.   I
beat the children in anger.  I
quarrel with my husband.  Hey Baba, I don't
beat my husband, no, no, I do
n't beat my husband, I
consider my husband as God [laughs]
but still if you
consider him as God then why do you fight, I do
n't fight with my husband, I get so angry, I don't know about what I am
angry about, I get
angry only with boys, I have an
eight year old daughter, I
beat her too [laughs]
no, I must get angry on some issue,
I don't know, but I get angry on small issues, so it gets angry on
small issues, right?
Yes.
So he talked big.   If you
talk big, your in-laws will throw you out.
[laughter]
Just imagine what the world is like?   That's
correct.   If you
cry in front of the world, they will ask why are you crying
?
And even if you laugh, there is a problem.  [laughter] Do
you want to get married?
Yes, I want to get married.   Are you in a
hurry?  No, it is not that early, but the fact is that the
age is increasing, nowadays
where is the age of a man, he gets over it in 40 to 45, that is
right, so you are thinking that now he is getting married and enjoying
worldly pleasures, at
least his child is 10 11 12 14 15 years old
[laughs]
how old is your child, if he is
not married yet [laughs]
no you are saying, not a 14 year old child,
14 15 years old means he will become a child,
oh baba yes yes.
Until the turn comes to deal with it.  [laughter]
So by the time you have a 14, 15-year-old,
you're going to be miserable.
What has happened?
What are you thinking like this?
Hey stay young.
Hey, these days, where can a man live beyond 45
?  Or
hey, these are the people who are eating more pizza and burgers.
These
pizza and burger vendors are selling it for Rs 40-50.
Hey! God.   The
man here is eating sprouted gram.   He is
eating salad and cucumber, he is walking 70, the ones who eat
gram are the ones who eat dal, puri, dal and roti.
Good.
So you don't eat pizza or burger.  Chowmein?
Not water puri.  Yes.  Then you'll go 60
70 yes.  These pizza burger and chowmein sellers are
dealing in 45, 50, 55 rupees.
We also tell them to use less of all the
flour items like pizza, burger etc.
Especially children are
eating samosas and pakoras as quickly as they can.
Meaning all this will be decided within 50-60 days.
Hey, it's going to be 40.
[laughter]
Just yesterday my friend passed away at the age of 35.
Why did he have an attack? He was silent
and used to eat pizza.
Yes, do
n't do this my love.   He did
not eat pizza, chowmein, meat etc. at all.   He did
not eat bread.
Yes, I don't eat bread.
This is all he used to eat.   There was an
attack.   There was an
attack.
So if you guys also want to die quickly then
eat pizza and burger.  [laughter]
Eat slowly.   If you want to
live long then eat gram.  By marking it.
Eat gram, eat some almonds, some home-cooked dal,
eat home-cooked roti, will you eat market food?  The
story ends in 50.  50 The story is over Radhe
[laughs]
Guruji
Radhe Radhe Radhe Guruji
I have come from Delhi to listen to your Maiya So
you are the Maiya [laughs]
No I like it very much from your mouth
when you say like this Maiya
[laughs]
Maiya
[laughs] I am
not married
No in that she married someone else.
[laughter] By
lying to me.   Then there was that
China model.
[laughter]
What was that?
China model.
You hold the branded one.
Good
branded from a good company.
No, India.
Listen, your parents will find a good boy for you too.   Yes.
Well, should this boyfriend
get involved with girlfriend?   Should
not fall.  Now you understand, right?
[laughter] It had
n't come before.   I had
said earlier that I would get married.
Yes sir, I had said that I will get married.  Sorry,
not sorry, Guruji.  [laughter]
Did I
say that at first, but then later I said that
my family would not agree.
Well,
he must have found someone more beautiful than you.
His ghost is like Kali.  Datto is C.
His teeth are also out.
Jai Baba.  [laughter] He
's a big idiot, he would have at least taken a
good model, he was
leaving me [laughter]
So even after leaving you, he
thinks that I'm a million times better,
yet he left you [laughter] He
says he left me for the family, it's a good thing,
everyone should do things for their family, what he says
is right [laughter]
So will you do it for your family or not?
Yes, I definitely will, so
now I won't get involved with anyone,
no, I won't
eat at all, I swear on my mother [music]
Now I will make friends with anyone only after marriage, I wo
n't get married, I will get
married, then after marriage, my husband
is my husband, no one else, a
good
husband, my husband, my God,
first get a husband… [laughter] I haven't got a
husband yet, no,
Guruji, he will become one,
oh no, let
God bless you, I just met a branded husband,
thank you, Guruji, I just
met China once,
Radhe Radhe Radhe Radhe
Maaa
[laughter]
My question is that whenever I
talk about marriage, I get girls who eat meat, eggs, etc., what has happened,
okay, so you want to get married,
yes  Yes, why do we have to get married,
why do we get married, tell me, I am
stuck, that is why I get married, so that I feel like it, why can't I get married
without marriage, it is not possible to do it
alone [laughs] come on, I hope
God gives you a good bride, I don't want an
egg eater, no, you bastard, I do
n't want a meat eater, and not a liquor drinker
[laughter],
and not someone who pushes,
and someone who packs in a drum, and grinds in a mixer
[laughter], the one who
packs in a cylinder, says
Radhey-Radhe,
oh my god, I
want a Radhey one, the one who says Radhey-Radhe is right
[laughter]
Guruji, can women blow the conch
[music] do
you want to blow it, I will blow it, that is why I am
asking, so what does
conch belong to your relationship,
oh no
conch, are you Lakshmi's Lakshmi or not,
and conch is Lakshmi's brother,
so what does conch belong to your relationship,
brother, why does one have to blow it?  [laughter]
Shankha is Lakshmi's brother.
Women do not blow the conch because
he is your brother by relation.
Okay [laughs]
we don't
play it.  Everyone refuses
but sometimes when no one is at home, they
play it.
[laughter]
wanted to deal with him.   Do
n't you love your younger brother [laughs]?   We do.
Come on, say I love you.  [laughter]
Say I love you.
I love you.   Do
n't do this my love.
Speak a little louder.
I love you.  [laughs]
Listen, you should also tell your wife I love you.
Guru ji, suppose I am going somewhere to
earn money.  That's all fine, earn money, son, your
wife is good, she is
very good, the poor girl has said it, go straight, tell your
wife I love you,
I love you [music] You
Jai Baba,
why are you saying it looking at me,
look at your wife [laughter]
say I love you,
I love you,
you live with love, don't complain,
your wife is good,
Guru ji, never give a rude reply, I go to the
temple in the morning and evening, after talking nonsense to anyone,
listen to my wife, now give a straight reply, not a rude one, okay, I will
come home from the temple,
Guru ji, first tell this to them, first explain to the
son, boy, first explain to the son.   I will
explain it to the boy also.  Explain to the child that he does
not go astray.  Don't get too carried away by your
parents.   From
now on, you should
respect your father over me.  This
is sanskar [music].
Climb on me right now.  He beats
me.
What has happened?  This
son will kill his mother.
What will he do when he grows up?   He
beats me.  I go to school and complain to my mother and
then I come back.
Yes.  You go to school and complain.
Then I will complain to his madam.
Where do you go to complain?
Madam, what about them?
Where?
In school.
[laughter] In
school,
yes in school, I
mean in school I complain about her to her madam, she is
right, she is right, go to school [laughter]
and complain to everyone you meet in school,
oh baba, the school people will explain, why won't they
explain, the school people will explain,
and the school people will explain, I am not coming,
tell the principal, you keep sitting in school, you do
n't explain [laughter] the
school people will explain, and who will explain, may God make
you happy like this [music], stay happy, Guru
ji, you are explaining to her well,
you should also go to school
[laughter]
I am not ready to tell anyone, she will
come from some house, she will gossip, she will come and then she will not give, she lies every
moment,
well, our
family is like this, one who lies [laughter] I am
always at loggerheads with my wife over small things, do
you fight with your wife over small
things, I feel that my wife does
not listen.  The wife [laughs] thinks
I don't listen.
What has happened?
Then you will do this, you shut up.
Raise your finger.
[laughter] Shut up.   May I get a
little of your blessings too.   Get me to
talk.
Radhe-Radhe Guru ji.   Yes.
What is the problem with your husband?  He just
shouts at every little thing
and
I don't like him shouting like that.  Good.
[laughter]
Shouting loudly.
Not by shouting.  Don't talk like a crow.
[laughter]
Speak like a cuckoo.  Look
how good speech God has given you.
Why croak like a frog or [laughter] how do you
sound like a cuckoo?
Sweet.
And the crow?   The
crow shouted.
So how do you speak?  Like a cuckoo,
like a crow?   I
speak only by shouting.
Crow, was there a crow in the field?
[laughter] I don't know.
That is why this habit has been formed from the previous life.
Or
you improve a little.  Now speak sweetly.   You are a
human being now, not a crow.
Guruji, please tell him a little so that he can
listen and understand what I am saying.   Just listen to it.
I hear that Guru ji also knows this.
Okay,
understand it.
I listen, I listen.  [laughs]
What I have, Guruji, is that there is pressure of business.  There is
pressure from home and family.
Mother and father are old.   You have to do
business but do
n't take out the pressure of business by fighting at home.  [laughter]
I teach arena to little kids.
Meaning, I teach wrestling, celibacy, everything for free.
Never took any money.
Or but
today, being the master of all, I myself am
entangled in a question.
What has happened?
Meaning I have lost my religion.  So you tell me
what should I do?
What happened?
Maharaj ji, I fell in love
with a girl.
Hey Baba, you
even taught sword fighting to the girl.
Yes, I have taught that too.  She is a devotee of Bhavani Mata.
I am also a devotee.  I fell in love with ours.
What happened after that?  So she
promised to marry me first and I told her
that I am not that kind of guy.  I am a
celibate.  I will only accept my better half.  I will
give her my love.  I
told her and she also came to my house in front of everyone.
Good.
Then the discussion about our relationship also took place in the same way,
but what came to his mind?  He
told him that he wanted to do a job.  I am studying.   Then
I cannot marry you.  He said
forget me.  [laughter]
So I was just completely shocked.  Meaning I did
not even go to the Akhara.  Listen, you are such a
great devotee.  You do such a good job.
In earlier times,
whom did Indra send to disturb the penance of sages and saints?  Tell.
Yes it is equal.
Whom did you send?
Maharaj ji used to send Apsara.
[laughter]
In this way you worshipped Hanumanji a lot.  Indra was
afraid that you might occupy the throne of Indra.
What?   That is
why Indra sent an Apsara into your life also.
She ruined you and left.
[laughter]
No, but that's the thing, I did
n't worship celibacy this year.  Otherwise
my birthday is on Hanuman Jayanti.
You should not stop worshipping Hanumanji.  Don't leave your work, keep working.
No, but I still have a problem with Hanuman ji.
Hey Baba, why do you mean it?  That I am no longer a
celibate.  I
What did I say to him?  If I get her, she is my
wife.
I will touch you only if I get her equal
because I am pure for her.  I don't
want anyone else.  Although I
also got good ones from him.
You had a relationship with that girl.  Yes, I
mean he had a relationship with me.  I did
n't understand anything, I mean she used to come to our house every day.
How many years was this relationship?
No, the year doesn't matter but love happens
in a moment.  [laughs]
But she used to come with me every three or four months.   It would have happened
in two moments.  You did not love your mother.   I
love my mother, that's why I am alive.
Hey! God.
When I cried every night, did
n't I fall in love with Hanumanji?
Yes, I love them too, right?  Maharaj ji,
I served Mother Goddess.   Do you
love Hanuman ji?  Or not?  Do
n't break away from Hanuman ji, make friends with the
girl you are breaking away from
Maharaj ji, I will love Hanuman ji only
when this body of mine has become impure,
now
when it will become pure,
tell me this when that girl has cheated you, then
why are you running after her [sangeet], it is
true,
I did not run after her, but what could be her
compulsion, Maharaj, she did not cheat, that
girl is also not bad, Maharaj,
or you can
marry her, I am Daya, I told her
[laughter], she says I do
not go in front of my parents, I said okay,
I will touch the feet of your parents [laughter] I will do
anything.
Yes, convince that girl.  You tell him to
bring it and I will explain it to him.  Brother, this is
my request to the girls.  Why do I
trap boys in the web of love [music] and then
leave them?  The poor guy [laughs] was heartbroken.
Maharaj ji, I am saying that I have been married for 11 years.
Good.
And my wife creates trouble with us every two days.
What has happened?
I love my wife so much.  And
then we are searching outside.  We don't
get anyone.  So tell me what to do?  So
who else are you looking for when you have a wife
?  [laughter]
It doesn't do it to us.  She creates a lot of trouble with us every two to three days.
[laughter]
Why?   If something like this happens, she
ruins her father's life completely.
Well,
we have brought some gruel.  It has been two-three days and in that
too I saw the eyes twice.   Okay yes.
What happened after that?
Then we went down a little bit.
You rolled your eyes.
Yes.  Otherwise they could have been reduced to ashes by water.
Otherwise she would tell us later [laughs] and
even beat us.   She does
n't kill.  She glares at me and says she will go to her parents' house.   Do
n't do this my love.
I will go to my parents' house.  You keep watching.
Yes.  Where did you talk to your wife?
Then we are looking for another place.  Then we are not even getting it.
[laughter]
The wife ran away.  Not there.  If we think about it, if it's the one on the outside, we'll
keep the one on the inside [encouraging voice].
[laughter]
So you mean you're in a neighborhood setting?
Yes, yes, if she behaves like this then
I am thinking of going outside also.
So it means the wife is the one who behaves badly.
Looking for a neighbor?  Did not start searching for God.  Take
refuge in the name of God.  You will go to the
neighbor.
We think that everything will be fine after that.
What?
Whose?   If I get
another one.   If you find
another one, you will not be destroyed.   Sorry sorry.
Like what happened to Ravana.  Yes yes and please tell my
wife where to talk to her
Radhe-Radhe Guru ji
how are you mother, I am
fine
why do you bother me,
no I bother you [laughs]
you bother me so much, she is saying that
I will get involved with someone else,
just to trouble me she is
saying this.
So why do you bother?
They don't want a little love, they will
understand a little to keep it.
Why is she loving your wife? If you are
not worshipping your wife, then why will you
love and worship her?  [Laughter] Please
understand a little, the
God of the house pampers and eats the laddu from outside [Music] The
wife is not getting love at home, so he
went to give love to the neighbour
[Laughter]
Talk to Kalu Ram, I want to tell him that just like
Parvati took care of Lord Shiva,
I want him to take care of me,
okay
you also take care of your wife,
I take care of her, that is why I have brought you
here to show you your darshan, it is
right but
why are you talking about leaving your wife, now your wife will also start
saying that I also
want to get involved with some other man.  You will like to
hear it.
This is a very good thing.
No, we did not ask him to leave.  We said
that if she doesn't love us then we will go
somewhere else.
Then your wife should also take someone else and say that
we will talk to him and live with him.
So would you like to hear it?
No.  [laughter]
Then things that don't feel good to hear should
not be said either.   Do you
understand?  You are telling your wife
that we can also get involved with someone else.
If your wife says that you
also stay and someone else looks after us, then
you will feel bad to hear it.
[laughs]
Husband, when we explain something, he doesn't listen to us.
What has happened?
Your husband doesn't listen to you?   I don't
believe it.
Talk to your husband.
Who is this husband?
Guru ji Radhe-Radhe.
So you don't listen to your wife.
All the money comes into his account, Guru
ji.  Hey Baba, should
mother
say something in front of you now,
why mother, you are sitting with all the money
[laughs], he
works for 18 hours, she says he doesn't talk, he
works, we ask, he doesn't talk for a month, he
puts money in our mobile,
but why,
and whatever he earns, he is giving it to you completely, he doesn't
remember, he is
not giving it to us, to
whom is he giving it, he has deposited it
in his account, he works after withdrawing from his account, he
gives a good house to the children, that there is no need to work,
brother, children should earn, why should their father give money to the children after
earning, the truth is,
you want to make the children handicapped?  Brother,
tell me, have your sons grown up?
They earn it.   If they
earn, they should spend their money on their children.
How long will the father keep earning and
giving?
This is what we are saying.
Whom?   The
husband does not listen to his own words.  He is after the boy.
What do you want to give to the boys?  Should I
give money to the children or not?
No, give me the money.
[laughs] I'll take
everyone home.
Tell me, don't you give money to your wife?
Gives.  Guruji, are you
saying this or not?  All the money is
in his account.   Do
n't do this my love.
Mother is saying let's keep it in our account.
And sometimes if we give him Rs. 40-500 together, he wo
n't even ask us [screaming voice]
where to spend it.
Okay, let's cover the
entire expense.
Yes, if we
spend Rs 500 on work worth Rs 5000 where it is not required to be done, then how will we manage our
household work.  [laughter]
Brother, it's very expensive.
Guru ji says that son and daughter-in-law will talk to
their children.  You don't bother about us,
son will,
okay your husband doesn't talk to you, it's been
a month, he hasn't talked to you, it's been two months, he hasn't talked to you, what has happened, what am I
hearing,
why should I make him talk, he hasn't talked to his husband for two months,
Guru ji, is there no point in lying now
[laughs] come on, tell your
wife I love you,
Guru ji, I took the Guru mantra yesterday, what did you say, I don't
lie, oh
brother, right now I am making you say I love you, oh, we will love your
husband right now,
say I love you, yes Guru ji, I love
you,
oh not to Guru ji [laughter]
wife I love you, okay, I have said I love you,
now listen
I love you, what am I hearing,
you also say I
love you, brother, husband
[laughter]
Guru ji, my question is that at night a
lady comes in my dream and sings a song.
Oh my God [laughs] she
says in Bhojpuri that I love you and it has been a
long time, it has been three-four years for me
[laughs]
who comes, some lady comes and sings a song, she
says pyar mein rara kahe bimar bani, you are
married, you are
married, so
your wife must be singing,
my wife does not sing but she
sings at night in my dreams and you also live there, what has happened, what am I
listening to this,
yes, so
what do I do in your dreams?
You sing and she also sings.  It's been many days.
[laughter]
Well, that was all I had left to do.
Yes, you completed that too.
[laughter] It's been
three years almost now.  I am suffering for three years.
So the witch comes?   The
witch does not come.  She says a lot somewhere.  She
says I love you.   When
I come, I don't go away.
Then she must have been your wife in your previous life.
Now only you know what I can say in this.
Hey, are you guys crazy?   She has been
coming to me regularly in my dreams for the last three years.   It
comes in dreams.  She doesn't even let me work
anywhere.  Meaning, we also talk face to face.   She
says whatever I want will happen.   It
also comes to the fore.
Yes.
So how does it look?
You come in front.  [laughter]
We're already in front.
You come forward.  We are in front of you, we are
here right now, you are in front of you there too,
oh, are you guys crazy, so we
come on TV every day at 3:00 in everyone's house, we
come on TV, we come there on the road also
[laughter] come on, there must be
someone coming, our ghost,
so we trouble you,
Maharaj ji, I am very troubled,
who troubles you, when
you come, I like the song
[laughter]
and if the ghost does not come, then
both of them, listen, when you sing, I like it, I
swear to God, keep
listening to it when I like it, what is the
problem, the
problem is that there is no money,
go there,
work, keep listening to songs, you also sing, you should
sing a song or two, you should recite Hanuman Chalisa,
Jai Hanuman Gyan Sagar
[laughter]
Hanuman says who is Hanuman,
you should recite Hanuman Chalisa in front of me, she will run away
[laughter] she does
not run away, I have read it and seen
Maharaj,
come on, recite Hanuman Chalisa, I do
not remember Hanuman Chalisa,
if I do not remember, then what will you recite, then how will she
run away, if I
tell her and she runs away,
okay  [laughter] That's what we are saying, if
you recite Hanuman Chalisa, you will run away.
Remember Hanuman Chalisa. Whenever she
sings the song Chudail, you start chanting Jai Hanuman
Gyan. She
sang a song, Bana ke jeans wali
Saliya Dulha Khojli
[laughter]
She sang Saree wali Saliya Dulha
Khojli. Will
you recite Hanuman Chalisa, what will you recite? I recite
Hanuman Chalisa also, still she does
n't run away.
Okay, let me tell you.  You don't even remember.
What will you tell me?
Maharaj ji, I remember Hanuman Chalisa.  I had to
keep it at home first.
Hey, when the witch comes, where will you look for her
?  Remember this.  [Laughter]
Maharaj Ji, how do I know that she talks to me 24 hours a day.
You just recite Hanuman Chalisa.  You'll be
bothering the witch yourself.  [laughter]
Maharaj Ji, I am looking for Lakshmi.
Okay
Lakshmi,
yes
Lakshmi is not available?
No,
why?
Which Lakshmi?  Lakshmi with money or
Lakshmi with wife [laughs]?
So you are not married?
Why didn't I do that, sir?  I will do it.
Asking parents to get it done.  [MUSIC]
Only the parents will know.
What has happened?  What am I hearing?
So I am not giving you Lakshmi,
so did you like someone
Maharaj Ji, did you like someone
I am God,
you are God, so
when there is God, then he already has
Lakshmi
[laughter]
then why are you getting worried [music]
now tell me what I do
n't have
[laughter]
what is not there I don't have
anything because I have seen a dream, which
Lakshmi,
which Lakshmi,
who did you see in the dream, which neighbor did you see
[laughter] I am
not getting up, the boy is going to get married
not getting up, I am sitting and sitting
here and looking for Lakshmi, first stand up,
you are not able to stand for two minutes
[laughter]
who will marry you in such a situation [laughter] if
no one will do it then
why are you looking for it, you chant Ram Ram,
yes chant the
name of God, you earn money,
how much do you earn
[encouraging voice] you
smoke ganja
[laughter]
no, you
drink liquor, you don't drink liquor, you do
n't drink ganja [laughter] I swear on my mother I do
n't drink liquor, you
smoke chillum,
hey chillum is ganja  Brother
[laughs]
your face tells me that you smoke
chillum.  How much chillum do you smoke?  [Music]
Sorry, any wrong words.
So those who smoke chillum are no longer eligible for marriage.  Do
n't get married now.  Look,
you don't have the courage.  I do
n't have the courage to stand up.  He went to find Lakshmi.
[laughter] It was a
mistake.  So she unknowingly said,
son, you are not able to recognize me,
I have recognized you, you are a number one ganjed
[laughs]
and how should I recognize you,
okay, okay,
go, do you want to say something, where are you going to smoke ganja
[laughs]
Guru ji, I have had a love marriage, that is why I have come to
you
[laughs] what have you come to tell you, you are
not sending my wife, I mean sorry [laughs]
what about me, tell me, you are not sending me, first get
married,
you are not ready to come home, mother is not sending me,
hey, what do you want to say, how old are you,
22 years
and wife's
18 years, so
when did you get married?   The
marriage took place eight days ago. It has been only
eight days since the marriage took place. Was it a
love marriage?
Yes,
you had a love marriage but now the girl's
parents will not send her.  That girl will
not agree to the courtyard.
Now the girl is ready to go to the courtyard but her parents are
not sending her.   The
reason for this is that Narendra Modi,
his brother, says don't come.
From which sister?
Yes.
So your wife has gone to her parents' house.
Ok.
And he is not ready to come.
[laughter]
So it got worse in 8 days.  It means they brought the Chinese model.   It got
spoiled.  [laughs]
Sir, he is a model from across the Ganga.
They don't say Ganga where there are sugarcanes.
So why did you do a love marriage?  Let's listen carefully.
Raji [laughs] died.
Well, the girl's parents were not ready.   I was
ready earlier, but not now.
And are your parents and
my parents agree?  Good.
My brother beat me up about it
but I didn't say anything.  I said let the
wedding procession take place.
His brother hit you.
My brother hit me but I did not say anything.
Okay, since you are married then bring her and keep her.
[laughter]
What drugs do they take?
Yes Guru ji does drugs.
What intoxication?
They eat gutkha and also drink alcohol.
Hey Baba, hey
boy, you have progressed a lot, let me talk to you.
[laughter]
Radhe-Radhe Guruji.
What is the name?
Akhilesh.   Do
you drink alcohol?
Good.
How much do you drink?   Worth
₹100.
Hey Baba, it's worth
What do you drink?
Listen, since when have you been drinking?
When did you start [laughs] from now on?   It's been
a year.   Do you
like alcohol?
No.  [laughs]
Where do you get ₹100 to drink alcohol?   I
earn it and bring it.
How much do you earn?   Do
people improve or deteriorate after spending ₹15,000 a month on alcohol?   Are
made.  [laughter] Are you
made after drinking alcohol?
No.  Do you make it?
Make it.   I made a
big mistake, sir.  [laughter] Do they get
worse?  What are they made of?   Are
made.
What are they made of?  What will happen after drinking alcohol
?
Not after drinking alcohol.   It is
not made by drinking alcohol.   It is
not possible.  People become spoiled after drinking alcohol.
Household matters deteriorate.
So son, will you become a drunkard?
[laughter]
No.
Why did you start it?  Who taught you to
drink alcohol?
Friends had taught me [laughs]
friend, is he your friend or an enemy? A
friend, the one who gives
you liquor, is he your friend or an
enemy,
now he has become an enemy
[laughs]
so son, the one who takes you on the wrong path is
not a friend, what is he?
We are showing you the right path, we
are your friends.  Well,
this liquor that they are giving you to drink is your
biggest enemy. They will
make you an addict by making you drink it, you will be useless. What they say is
right, if
you will not drink it, I will
definitely not drink it,
swear to my mother that you will not drink it,
say to my mother, I will not drink it
today, I will definitely not drink it, if I drink it, I will not drink it, if I drink it, my
mother will die, they will not let me die,
if I do not drink it, will I die, yes, [laughs]